Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(تَوأَم)
(Episode 14)
(الحلقة 14)
Ling Su. Come and take a look.
لينغ سو، تعالَ وألقِ نظرة.
How did Shao Yao bandage my wound? It's oozing blood again.
كيف ضمدت شاو ياو جرحي؟ ينزف دمًا من جديد.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Chief.
رئيس.
No wonder you can't get a girl.
لا عجب أنك لا تستطيع الحصول على فتاة.
At a time like this, you have to scheme to gain sympathy.
في مثل هذا الوقت، عليك أن تخطط لكسب التعاطف.
Here. I'll make your wound a little bigger.
ها أنا ذا سأجعل جرحك أكبر قليلا.
I don't believe she won't notice it then.
لا أعتقد أنها لن تلاحظ ذلك حينها.
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
I just can't feel pain. I'll still die if I lose too much blood.
لا أستطيع الشعور بالألم. سأموت إن فقدت الكثير من الدم.
Don't worry. I know what I'm doing.
لا تقلق، أنا أعرف ما أفعله.
Besides, I've already sent someone to tell Ms. Lu...
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، لقد أرسلت بالفعل شخصًا ليخبر السيدة لو...
you're critically injured and dying soon.
لقد تعرضت لإصابة خطيرة وستموت قريبًا.
When she gets here, just start the performance.
عندما تصل إلى هنا، فقط ابدأ الأداء.
No. When did you tell her?
لا متى قلت لها؟
Just now.
الآن.
She should be here soon.
ينبغي أن تكون هنا قريبا.
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
Chief!
رئيس!
You can't die!
لا يمكنك أن تموت!
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Chief!
رئيس!
You have to hang in there!
يجب عليك الصمود!
I thought you didn't feel pain.
اعتقدت أنك لم تشعر بالألم.
I have work to do at the Xuntian Sect.
لدي عمل يجب أن أقوم به في طائفة شونتيان.
I have to go back and feed the dogs.
يجب علي أن أعود وأطعم الكلاب.
What?
ماذا؟
Ling Su, you...
لينغ سو، أنت...
Get up now.
استيقظ الآن.
I can't take it anymore.
لا أستطيع أن أتحمل ذلك بعد الآن.
I really didn't mean to.
لم أقصد ذلك حقًا.
I just wanted you to visit me more.
أردت فقط أن تزورني أكثر.
If you're really that angry,
إذا كنت غاضبًا حقًا،
then stab me.
ثم طعنني.
But after you stab me,
ولكن بعد أن طعنتني،
this matter will all be over.
هذا الموضوع سوف ينتهي تماما.
You can't ignore me.
لا يمكنك تجاهلي.
You lied,
لقد كذبت
and you want to pay with your life.
وتريد أن تدفع بحياتك.
Master is indeed generous.
المعلم كريم حقا.
If I really die by your hand,
إذا متُّ حقاً على يدك،
I'll have no regrets.
لن أشعر بأي ندم.
Even if you can't feel pain,
حتى لو لم تشعر بالألم،
you must protect yourself.
يجب عليك حماية نفسك.
If the wound is too big and you lose too much blood,
إذا كان الجرح كبيرًا جدًا وفقدت الكثير من الدم،
you won't even know how you died.
لن تعرف حتى كيف مت.
How can you protect me for the rest of my life?
كيف يمكنك حمايتي لبقية حياتي؟
Actually, this whole thing was Ling Su's...
في الواقع، هذا الشيء كله كان من لينغ سو...
What did you just say?
ماذا قلت للتو؟
I said...
قلت...
I like you.
أنا معجب بك.
I'm willing to take a gamble on you.
أنا على استعداد للمقامرة معك.
I'm willing to risk my heart one more time.
أنا على استعداد للمخاطرة بقلبي مرة أخرى.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'd already planned it all out.
لقد خططت لكل هذا بالفعل.
I said...
قلت...
I'd deal with Situ Xian first.
سأتعامل مع Situ Xian أولاً.
Then I'd buy you a big mansion.
ثم سأشتري لك قصرًا كبيرًا.
Then I'd fill it with flowers.
ثم سأملأه بالزهور.
Then I'd properly confess my love to you.
ثم سأعترف لك بحبي بشكل صحيح.
I'm not prepared for what you've just said.
أنا لست مستعدًا لما قلته للتو.
Turn around and let me see you.
استدر ودعني أراك.
Look at me.
انظر إليَّ.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
I know about everything you've done.
أنا أعلم كل ما فعلته.
I've noticed it all.
لقد لاحظت كل ذلك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Let's be together from now on.
دعونا نكون معًا من الآن فصاعدًا.
Okay?
تمام؟
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I won't let you lose again.
لن أسمح لك بالخسارة مرة أخرى.
Okay.
تمام.
Don't push me away.
لا تدفعني بعيدا.
Lu Zhao.
لو تشاو.
After we deal with Situ Xian,
بعد أن تعاملنا مع Situ Xian،
marry me.
تزوجيني.
Okay?
تمام؟
Okay.
تمام.
- Hurry up. - What are you doing?
- اسرعي. - ماذا تفعلين؟
- Hurry up! - Ms. Lu may believe your lie,
- أسرع! - قد تصدق السيدة لو كذبتك،
but I don't. There's nothing wrong with Master.
لكنني لا أفعل. لا يوجد أي خطأ في المعلم.
It wasn't a big deal before.
لم يكن الأمر كبيرا من قبل.
But I'm afraid he's truly in danger now.
لكن أخشى أنه في خطر حقيقي الآن.
I'm doomed.
لقد حُكم علي بالهلاك.
I'm afraid I'm the one...
أخشى أنني أنا...
who's in danger this time.
من هو في خطر هذه المرة؟
You sure know how to pick a good time!
من المؤكد أنك تعرف كيفية اختيار الوقت المناسب!
Are you doing it again?
هل تفعل ذلك مرة أخرى؟
Well...
حسنًا...
Right.
يمين.
How is the situation with Situ Xian?
كيف هو الوضع مع سيتو شيان؟
He's too patient.
إنه صبور للغاية.
Since he got the Lu family's assets,
منذ حصوله على أصول عائلة لو،
he hasn't stepped out of his residence.
لم يخرج من مسكنه
Those Qiang people seem to be doing nothing out of the ordinary...
يبدو أن هؤلاء الناس تشيانغ لا يفعلون شيئًا خارجًا عن المألوف ...
besides drinking tea and talking business at the teahouse.
بالإضافة إلى شرب الشاي والتحدث عن الأعمال في المقهى.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
He's a fox.
إنه ثعلب.
He'll show his tail eventually.
سوف يظهر ذيله في نهاية المطاف.
We'll definitely expose him.
سوف نفضحه بالتأكيد.
We definitely will.
بالتأكيد سوف نفعل ذلك.
- Your Highness. - Speak.
- صاحب السمو. - تكلم.
I've investigated it.
لقد قمت بالتحقيق في الأمر.
Shao Yao is from the Xuntian Sect.
شاو ياو من طائفة شونتيان.
The guard you sent to Pilan Palace to monitor Lu Zhao...
الحارس الذي أرسلته إلى قصر بيلان لمراقبة لو تشاو...
was also killed long ago.
وقد قُتل أيضًا منذ زمن طويل.
The one who truly followed was...
والذي اتبع حقًا كان...
Xiao Ren.
شياو رن.
Xuntian Sect.
طائفة شونتيان.
You just wait and see!
انتظر فقط وشاهد!
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Speak!
يتكلم!
Ms. Liu refuses to take her medicine and go to sleep.
ترفض السيدة ليو تناول دوائها والذهاب إلى النوم.
She's making a fuss and demanding that you go and accompany her.
إنها تثير ضجة وتطلب منك أن تذهب وترافقها.
Did you not know that we are discussing official matters...
ألم تعلم أننا نتحدث في أمور رسمية...
right now?
الآن؟
Tell her...
أخبرها...
she shouldn't be arrogant because I spoil her.
لا ينبغي لها أن تكون متغطرسة لأنني أفسدها.
Get out.
اخرج.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Continue keeping an eye on Lu Zhao and the Xuntian Sect.
استمر في مراقبة لو تشاو وطائفة شونتيان.
I'll go check on her.
سأذهب للتحقق منها.
If anything happens,
إذا حدث أي شيء،
report to me at any time.
أبلغني في أي وقت.
Understood.
مفهومة.
I didn't expect you...
لم أتوقعك...
to know how to arrange flowers.
لمعرفة كيفية ترتيب الزهور.
Why is that surprising?
لماذا هذا مفاجئ؟
Women can wear armor.
يمكن للمرأة أن ترتدي الدروع.
Why can't men arrange flowers?
لماذا لا يستطيع الرجال ترتيب الزهور؟
I enjoy these refined activities.
أستمتع بهذه الأنشطة الراقية.
This is the first time I've heard...
هذه هي المرة الأولى التي أسمع فيها...
you say,,,
أنت تقول,,,
what you like.
ما تحبه.
From now on, the flowers in this manor...
من الآن فصاعدا، الزهور في هذا القصر...
are your responsibility.
هي مسؤوليتك.
I've received your orders.
لقد تلقيت أوامرك.
After leaving the Prince of Chu's manor,
بعد مغادرة قصر أمير تشو،
the world feels vast.
يبدو أن العالم واسع.
The world is so big.
العالم كبير جداً.
Why should women be forced...
لماذا يجب إجبار المرأة...
to stay in a small courtyard...
للبقاء في فناء صغير...
for their entire lives?
طوال حياتهم؟
You're right.
أنت على حق.
I believe that one day,
أعتقد أنه في يوم من الأيام،
everyone in this world...
الجميع في هذا العالم...
will be able to live freely.
سيكون قادرا على العيش بحرية.
- Candied haws! - Do you want some candied haws?
- زهر الزعرور المسكر! - هل تريد بعض الزعرور المسكر؟
Sweet and round candied haws!
زهرات مسكرة حلوة ومستديرة!
Shopkeeper!
صاحب المتجر!
Two candied haws, please.
اثنين من الزعرور المسكرة، من فضلك.
Coming!
آت!
Here.
هنا.
Let me.
دعني.
Sir.
سيد.
This is the Ruyi Hairpin that's in trend right now.
هذا هو دبوس الشعر Ruyi الذي هو في الاتجاه الآن.
Wear it for everything to go well.
ارتديها لكي تسير الأمور على ما يرام.
Quickly buy one for your wife!
اشتري واحدة لزوجتك بسرعة!
- I'm not his... - You're right.
- أنا لست له... - أنت على حق.
My wife deserves a blessed life.
زوجتي تستحق حياة مباركة.
You are so good to your wife.
أنت جيد جدًا مع زوجتك.
What a rare and blessed match!
يا لها من مباراة نادرة ومباركة!
Only when both of us are blessed...
فقط عندما نكون كلانا مباركين...
can we be together forever.
هل يمكننا أن نكون معًا إلى الأبد؟
The shopkeeper is watching.
صاحب المتجر يراقب.
You two are truly a loving couple.
أنتم حقا زوجين محبين.
A match made in heaven!
مباراة صنعت في الجنة!
Well said!
أحسنت القول!
Here's a reward!
وهنا المكافأة!
Thank you, sir! Thank you, ma'am!
شكراً لك يا سيدي! شكراً لك يا سيدتي!
Where else would you like to go, my wife?
أين تريدين أن تذهبي بعد هذا يا زوجتي؟
Your husband will accompany you to the end.
زوجك سوف يرافقك حتى النهاية.
I want to eat...
أريد أن آكل...
the Xizi glutinous rice balls from the east side of the city.
كرات الأرز الدبق Xizi من الجانب الشرقي للمدينة.
Xizi glutinous rice balls?
كرات الأرز الدبق Xizi؟
Is the shopkeeper bald?
هل صاحب المتجر أصلع؟
Yes.
نعم.
Wait for me here. I'll be right back.
انتظرني هنا، سأعود حالا.
Okay.
تمام.
Where are my seeds of longing?
أين بذور شوقي؟
No!
لا!
Miss.
يفتقد.
This is your bracelet, right?
هذا هو سوارك، أليس كذلك؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Miss.
يفتقد.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
This girl is so strange.
هذه الفتاة غريبة جداً.
Miss!
يفتقد!
She took poison?
هل تناولت السم؟
Miss.
يفتقد.
Why did you try to kill yourself?
لماذا حاولت قتل نفسك؟
My husband sold me to a brothel.
لقد باعني زوجي إلى بيت دعارة.
Although I've escaped,
على الرغم من أنني هربت،
where can I go?
أين يمكنني أن أذهب؟
I'm no longer chaste.
أنا لم أعد عفيفة.
I'm too ashamed to live.
أنا أشعر بالخجل الشديد من العيش.
If they catch me,
إذا أمسكوا بي،
I'll die anyway.
سأموت على أية حال.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Put me out of my misery.
أخرجني من بؤسي.
Why should women pay...
لماذا يجب على المرأة أن تدفع...
for men's sins?
لخطايا الرجال؟
It was never your fault.
لم يكن خطأك أبدًا.
Where do you live?
أين تعيش؟
I'll take you there.
سوف آخذك إلى هناك.
I'll see who dares to hurt you.
سأرى من يجرؤ على إيذائك.
You must not risk yourself for me.
لا يجب عليك المخاطرة بنفسك من أجلي.
I'm not worth it.
أنا لا أستحق ذلك.
No one should despise themselves.
لا ينبغي لأحد أن يحتقر نفسه.
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Why are you back?
لماذا عدت؟
Who's going to make me money if you come back?
من الذي سيجعلني أحصل على المال إذا عدت؟
I think you have a death wish!
أعتقد أن لديك رغبة في الموت!
Where did this wench come from?
من أين جاءت هذه الفتاة؟
You're interfering in our matters!
أنت تتدخل في شؤوننا!
Don't come near us!
لا تقترب منا!
Don't...
لا...
Don't you dare touch my savior!
لا تجرؤ على لمس منقذي!
Savior?
المخلص؟
I'm going to kill you.
سأقتلك.